ROBEL TESFAMICHAEL HAWELTI

Address:

1145 Wereda 15, Kolfe-Keranyo, Addis Ababa

Phone:

+251920038683

Email:

robelhawelti@aol.com

Profile

Junior IT Technician and programmer specialized on computer maintenance, web designing, database management, and networking. Experienced with Network installation and management, and computer maintenance. Strong background in the IT department and steadily growing experience especially in the Web-Aplication designing and management field.

Skill Highlights

- Punctual and Disciplined
- Quick Learner
- Highly Adoptive

- Team Player
- Complex Problem Solver
- Composed Under Stress

Experience

Computer Application and Maintenance Instructor – 05/2021 to date Jesuit Refugee Service, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

Junior IT Technician - 09/2019 to 04/2021 Nahim Pharmaceuticals PLC, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

Junior Network Technician - 11/2017 to 02/2019

RCC, Asmara, Eritrea

Computer Application Instructor - 02/2017 to 10/2017 **Adi-Halo Post-secondary Technical Institute**, Adi-Halo, Eritrea

Education

Technical Institute: Computer Maintenance and Networking - 2016

Halay Technical Institute, Asmara, Eritrea

Online: Google IT Support Professional Certificate - 2021

Google, Coursera

Online: Web Design for Everybody, Specialization - 2021

University of Michigan, Coursera

Languages

English – Excellent

Tigrigna – Excellent

Amharic - Good

Arabic - Beginner